It's now or never, motherfuckers!
要就现在 否则永不 混蛋
We end this shit tonight.
今晚就结束这一切
"Destroy everything."
"销毁一切"
Is this the message we want to send our children
我们想发送给后代们 如此信息吗
for generations to come?
世代以来
"Destroy... everything."
"摧毁一切"
This, ladies and gentlemen,
此物 女士们先生们
is what that weapon-wielding goon wore the night of the altercation.
是挥舞武器的恶棍 当晚穿的
Looks to me like he was on a mission to kill.
在我看来 他是在执行杀人任务
Combat boots,
战斗靴
war chains...
铁链
And this.
还有这个
"Destroy everything."
"销毁一切"
How's it going, new york?
纽约 怎么样
I chose to speak to you in a square because I think we're kind of conditioned to listen to people,
我之所以选择电视 因为我们必须适应听众
when they're in the shape of a square.
听众喜欢聚集在各种显示器前
And also, here in hollywood,
何况好莱坞
this is where we give people what they want.
是让人们梦想成真的地方
Violence, I guess that's what it seems to come down to.
他们所要的 我归结于一点 即暴力
What I wanted to talk to everyone today about,
今天我想和大家谈谈
uh... I don't really want to preach,
我真的不想说教
I just want to, more, bring up some questions.
我只是想多提些问题
And since I always tend to be a scapegoat, I thought we'd talk about blame.
因为我总是倾向于做替罪羊 我们谈谈责怪吧
Right now, everybody wants to blame music,
现在 每个人都想责怪音乐
they want to blame movies,
他们想责怪电影
but, uh... you know,
但是
we've forgotten that we have a dead guy hanging from a tree in our living rooms.
我们忘了自己的起居室里 有一棵吊着死人的树
And that's something that we've worshipped all our lives.
这是我们一生所崇拜的东西
If you think about the crucifix as the...
如果你认为十字架为
The greatest mass-market piece of merchandise in the history of the world.
世界史上最大规模的商品市场
I've always found it to be kind of interesting.
我一直觉得这很有趣
We haven't really sat down and talked about that on the news.
我们从没坐稳 在新闻上谈过这一点
Um... also, wondered why nobody cares when an adult commits some senseless act of violence
还有 为何无人关心成年人犯无意义暴力行为时
they want to have a reason why.
却不问为什么
That's only when a kid does it.
仿佛只有孩子才会这么做
But I think what's really...
但我认为真正
Begun to confuse people now
现在混淆人们的
and why we're in this state of... uh, chaos
以及为什么我们处于混乱...
and, uh, pc, nonsensical, uptightness.
吸毒 荒谬 暴躁的状态
It's white teenagers.
而白人青少年
That's the real enigma.
才是真正的谜
Why are they mad?
他们为什么发怒
They're middle class,
他们是中产阶级
they're white, they're spoiled.
他们是白人 他们被宠坏了
Is it because they know america's a lie?
是因为他们知道美国是个谎言吗
Is it because we make them feel
是因为我们让他们觉得
like they're never good enough, you know?
好像他们永远都不够好
"You're never good enough for the scholarship,
"你永远不够好 不能拿奖学金
for the car, for the girl.
车 还有姑娘
Never good enough to be famous for 15 minutes."
从来不够好 哪怕15分钟"
And then, are we surprised why they're mad
然后 我们又惊讶于他们为什么发怒
or why they end up dead, you know?
或者为什么他们最终暴毙
Why the violence?
为什么要暴力
'Cause, you know...
因为 你知道
You made them, america.
是你驱使的 美国
You know, what do you expect?
你能期待什么呢
Come on, get your game day sports stuff.
来买 比赛日运动装备
Shit, yeah.
妈的
Hey, quit messing around, man.
别胡闹了 伙计
Why? I don't even see why your bitch-ass needs a helmet anyway.
干嘛 你屁股还需要头盔吗
Jv has no business suiting up.
JV连合适的装备都没有
Come on now, ricky.
拜托 里奇
He might see the field.
说不定他会上场的
We'll have their ass beat by halftime, you know that.
我们会在中场休息前揍扁他们的
Mccormick, you act like it's hard to be a lineman, man.
麦考克 做前锋有那么难吗
All you do is sit on your fat ass and eat.
你只会屁股蹲 坐着吃饭
Buddy, only thing I'm eating is your mom's pussy.
哥们 我只吃你妈的逼
What... get... get the fuck off me!
你他妈的给我滚开
Quit freakin' playing grab-ass, man!
别再玩抠菊花了 兄弟
It's a playoff game!
现在是平分决赛
Act like it!
走点心
Let it go, cody.
算了吧 科迪
Come on, let's bring it in, men.
来吧 获得胜利去 兄弟们
Our father, who art in heaven,
我们的父 以天之名
hallowed by thy name.
以你的圣名
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done,
你的国来了 你的旨意将完成
on earth as it is in heaven.
在尘世 一如天堂
Give us this day our daily bread.
赐予我们每天的面包
And forgive us our trespasses,
赦免我们的罪过
as we forgive those who trespass against us.
因为我们原谅那些得罪我们的人
And lead us not into temptation,
带领我们不要陷入诱惑
but deliver us from evil.
把我们从邪恶中解救出来
For thine is the kingdom,
因为你是国
the power, the glory forever
是力量 是荣耀 永远
and ever. Hey, what's up, bri?
永远 - 怎么了
Good to see you, man.
很高兴见到你 伙计
Where you been? New york.
你去哪了 纽约
Good, yeah. The show's already going on.
很好 演出已经开始了
The show must go on!
演出必须继续
Hey, what's up, man?
怎么了 伙计
My brother inside? Yeah, he's in there somewhere.
我兄弟在里面吗 - 在 某处躲着
How we looking?
怎么样
Uh, good...
很好
What's up, dawg?
你好 伙计
What the fuck!
搞什么
Dude! Oh!
伙计
Brian?
布莱恩
Brian! Dude!
布莱恩 伙计
No, no, no, I ain't letting you off that easy.
不 我不会让你好过的
Get your ass up here and do the song list.
你死过来开唱
Get up here.
快上来
Let me tell you something about this dude right here...
这家伙 我告诉诸位
We wouldn't be here if it wasn't for this kid right here!
如果不是他 我们是不会在这里的
Cheers, bro.
干杯 兄弟
Hey, you got a light?
有打火机吗
You know those things take 14 minutes off your life
这玩意每次14分钟 让你出窍
every time you smoke one of them?
你每抽一支时 你知道吗
What are you, a psychic?
你是灵媒吗
I only smoke when I drink.
我只喝酒时抽烟
Yeah, how much have you had to drink tonight?
你今晚喝了多少酒
Well, I'm sorry, the guy who can down a 40 ounce beer in like five seconds
抱歉 那个五秒内灭掉40盎司啤酒的家伙
is questioning me about drinking?
居然质问我喝酒?
Well, you know what they say, a bottle of malt liquor a day keeps the doctor away.
古人有云 一天一瓶麦芽酒 气的医生满地爬
Really? And how many bottles
真的么 那么多少瓶
have you had tonight?
你今晚灭掉?
Don't worry about it.
这你别担心
Look at this fucker.
看看这个混蛋
What's happening, man?
怎么了 伙计
Shit, I didn't think you'd make it back in time.
妈的 没想到你能及时回来
I'm not gonna miss the show.
我不会错过演出的
Thought we lost you to the road.
以为我们把你丢在路上了
Psh. Should've known this black hole would suck you back in.
就知道黑洞 会把你吸进去的
Never fails.
每次必中
Killer show.
杀手秀
Glad to have you back.
很高兴你回来了
Fuck yeah, dawg.
他妈的 伙计
Fuck.
他妈的
Fucked my ankle up in there.
我又回来了
Shut the fuck up, king, all right?
闭嘴 国王 好吗
Dude.
伙计
All right, sunshine,
好的 阳光
tell this asshole that skinheads are racist.
告诉这个混蛋 光头党是种族主义者
First of all,
首先
stop calling me"sunshine."
别再叫我"阳光" 了
Read a fucking book.
其次 去读读书
This shit was started way before any of that racist shit came around.
光头党早于种族主义狗屎
He's right, it goes way back. Straight up, though.
他是对的 确实如此
Straight-laced bitch.
确实个婊
Okay, fuck y'all.
好了 操
Crass, let's roll, come on.
走吧
Catch up with y'all in a bit.
一会见
Yo, help me clean some shit up.
帮我擦点东西
Hey! There he is!
他在那儿
Tiny human.
小人儿
What's up, dude? What's your name?
怎么了伙计 你叫什么名字
What's up? Jake.
咋的 杰克
Digging that hat. Oh, this?
帽子不错 - 这个么
Yeah, it's pretty sweet.
是啊 很赞
You have a good time at the show?
演出开心吗
It was a damn good show.
真是个好演出
Actually, it's my first show.
事实上 这是我看的第一次演出
No fucking way. Yeah.
不会吧 - 是的
I got an idea.
我有个主意
Come with me. Come on.
跟我来 快
Yo. Yo, I want to introduce you to my little buddy, jake.
介绍你 我的小伙伴 杰克
He just got his concert cherry popped tonight.
今晚的演唱会 他是处女看
Hell yeah, little dude.
是么 小伙计
You have a good time?
开心吗
Yeah, for sure.
当然
Starting them young, love it.
真年轻 不错
That's how we do it. Yeah.
我们就是这样
Hey, would you sign my hat?
能在我的帽子上签名吗
Of course.
当然
Here you are.
给你
Yo, thanks. You got it, bro.
谢谢 - 给你 兄弟
That's what's up.
就是这样
See you later. All right. Yo...
回头见 好吧
It's not much...
不多
Ah. ...But here's your cut.
但这是你那份
Hell yeah. Thanks, man.
当然了 谢了 伙计
Long as we make it to the 505, it's all good. That should do the trick.
只要能到505就行 - 那应能成功
Dude...
伙计
Thank you.
谢谢
You got it. Killer show.
没问题 杀手秀
Well, unless you've been living under a rock,
除非你住在石头下面
I'm sure you heard the outcome of tonight's 5-8
我敢肯定 你听到今晚第5-8名次的结果
division I quarterfinal playoff game
即一级联赛 季后赛的四分之一决赛
between the rebels and the rabbits,
介于叛军队和兔子队之间
and boy was it ugly.
结果是
That is, if you were rooting for the rebels.
如果你为叛军队加油
46 to 3, you heard that right, folks.
46比3 你听得没错 伙计们
Better luck next season, rebels.
下个赛季运气会更好 叛军队
What do y'all want to do now?
你们现在想做什么
I guess get wasted. I mean, what's better to do in this town?
虚度光阴 我是说 这镇子能干什么
Yeah, it's been a while since I've had a beer.
我已经有一段时间没喝啤酒了
Yeah, well, it's now or never.
要就现在 要就永不
What time is it?
现在 几点钟
Fuck.
他妈的
It's 12:15.
12:15
Son of a bitch.
狗娘养的
Dumbass laws, man.
白痴法律 伙计
Frosty!
冷冰冰
What's up, boss? What up, what up?
你好哇
Hey, you got to come to our next show, bro.
你得来看我们下一场演出 兄弟
I'm telling you, you'll love it.
你会喜欢的
Thanks, boss.
谢了 老板
Fuck yeah. It's gonna take a lot of praying
他妈的 需要多祈祷
to fix that freak show. Fucking pussies.
才能搞定怪胎秀 该死的娘娘腔
For you, princess.
给你 公主
For you.
给你的
Me first.
我先
My love.
给你 我的爱
Aw, how sweet.
真贴心
Bro-bro.
哥们儿
You know, I think that we should give it a try,
我们该试一下
you know what I'm saying? Me and you together...
知道我在说什么吗 你我...
Yeah. Maybe.
耶 也许
Yeah! She said"yes"!
她说"耶"
What's up, faggot? Fuck around and find out.
怎么了 基佬  - 不会自己看吗
You're a fucking freak, man.
你他妈怪胎 伙计
Fucking pussy.
死娘炮
Fucking tweaker reeks. What's wrong with him?
毒瘾的臭味 他有病吗
That bitch-ass motherfucker's about to get fucking boxed, dawg.
那婊子要被打得屁滚尿流了 哥们儿
Which one? That fucking bitch-ass right there with the fucking tie.
哪一个 - 系领带的那个
Those fucking losers, man.
鲁蛇们 伙计
Think they might like you, cody.
他们可能喜欢你 科迪
Fuck you, mccormick.
去你的 麦考克
You got my nightstick, bro?
你带了我的警棍吗 兄弟
Yeah.
有啊
Aw, you piece of shit.
你这坨屎
What, bitch?
干嘛 婊子
Fuck you.
操
Oh, yeah? What's up, what's up?
怎么了
What, bitch?
干嘛 婊子
Dude, chill the fuck out, dawg. What, bitch?
伙计 冷静点 伙计 干嘛 婊子
Do something. Let's get the fuck out of here.
做点什么 我们离开
Do something, bruh. Fuck you too, bitch.
做点什么 兄弟 操你妈的 婊子
Do something, bruh. Whoa,"bitch"?
做点什么 兄弟 "婊子"是吗
I'm trying to maintain the peace, dawg.
我想和平的 伙计
You don't want to fuck with me, fool.
你别惹我 笨蛋
If it's on, it's fucking on.
惹了就别怪我不客气
Suck my dick, you fucking freak show.
吸我的老二 该死的怪胎秀
"Freak show"? I'll show you freak show
"怪胎秀" 我给你看怪胎秀
when I bash your dome in, bruh. Huh?
等我顶你个肺 老弟
I'm gonna bash your fucking dome in, dawg!
揍扁你脑袋 老弟
Hey, god damn it.
见鬼
Hey, hey, take it outside!
都出去
Let's go, outside!
出去
I'm calling the damn cops. Outside!
我要报警了 出去
Hey, what now, bitch? I'm gonna fuck you up.
咋的了 婊子 我要弄死你
Where you going, dawg?
你要去哪里 老弟
Where you going, man?
去哪 老弟
Yo, you're lucky your faggot fucking friends are here to save you.
你真走运 你的同性恋朋友来救你了
Oh, they got nothing to do with this, man.
他们和这事无关 伙计
This got everything to do with you, me,
这一切都与你我有关
that pussy-ass look on your face and my fucking friend here, man!
你摆什么臭脸 老弟
Oh, you like that? Fuck you,
你喜欢吗 操你妈
you fucking piece of shit.
该死的混蛋
That's right, bitch.
没错了 婊子
That's right.
没错
Roll the fuck out.
赶紧滚
Roll the fuck out, bruh.
滚出去 老弟
The fuck you going, bruh? Yo!
你他妈的去哪 老弟
Fuck yeah, that's right, bitch!
他妈的 没错 婊子
Hey, he's coming back,
他回来了
he's coming back, he's coming back.
他回来了 他会回来的
Get the fuck out of here.
快滚
Please tell the court how you would describe yourself,
请向法庭描述你自己
your lifestyle.
你的生活方式
I don't know.
我不知道
Punk?
朋克
"Punk"?
"朋克"
Funny you would say that.
真好笑你会这么说
Because webster's dictionary...
根据韦伯斯特字典
Gives us the following definition of this term
该术语具有以下定义
you so eloquently use to describe yourself: Punk.
你居然雄辩地形容你自己: 朋克
"A worthless person;
"一文不值的人"
an often aggressive or violent young man,
好斗或暴力的年轻人
usually a petty hoodlum or gangster;
通常是小流氓或匪徒
a sociopath."
反社会者
It's not about a definition.
这不是定义
I wouldn't expect someone like you...
我不期待你这种人
To understand that.
能理解
Oh, well, then please help me.
那么请帮帮我
Help the jury understand how wearing chains and military clothing is just part of the style,
帮助陪审团了解 穿链子和军服 属于穿衣风格
and not weapons at the ready.
而不是武器准备就绪
It's a statement.
这是个声明
Oh, you are correct,
你说对了
it most certainly is a statement.
这当然是一个声明
But it is not a statement of fashion,
但它不是时尚声明
it's a statement of malicious intent.
而是恶意意图的声明
My head's pounding.
我脑袋在响
It's not your head, man, there's someone at the door.
不是你的头 伙计 有人在敲门
Herschel, what's happening, man?
赫歇尔 怎么了 伙计
What's the deal?
什么情况
Rent was due last week.
房租上周到期
Ah, I know, I do.
我知道 我有的
I got a little behind.
我有点迟了
Here's this.
给你
It's short.
不够
I know.
我知道
But just give us a little bit more time,
不过再给我们点时间
and I promise I'll get you the rest.
我保证把剩下的给你
I like you all and what you're doing and all,
我喜欢你们
but I need the money.
但我需要钱
I can't have y'all squatting in here.
我不能让你们蹲在这里
I'm already giving you a break on price, man.
我已经给你价格冰点了 伙计
I know.
我知道
And we appreciate it.
我们很感激
I'm just... I'm trying.
我只是 我在努力
You know, it's...
你知道...
Dude, you know I'm good for it.
兄弟 你知道我很擅长的
These shows, they're starting to go really well.
演出很顺利
I just need like a week and I'll figure it out.
我只需要一周时间 我会想办法的
All right, but that's it.
好吧 但到此为止
All right? I'm serious this time.
好吗 这次我是认真的
I honestly can't wait any longer, all right?
我真的不能再等了 好吗
One week or I got to lock it up, man.
一周或者我得锁门 伙计
Okay. And, herschel, thank you.
好的 赫歇尔 谢谢你
I promise, you won't regret this.
我保证你不会后悔的
All right. I promise.
好吧 我保证
Thank you.
谢谢
One week!
一周
You know, it's gonna be hard for you to get a job looking like a wild indian.
搞得像土著印第安人 你很难找工作的
Don't worry about me, old man, I got a few things lined up.
别担心我 老伙计 我有很多活儿要干
Oh, I'm not worried, that's your mother's job.
我不担心 那是你妈的工作
I guess a helmet's out of the question, too.
我想头盔也没问题了
I'm not trying to look like an idiot.
我并不想扮白痴
You could've fooled me.
你本可以吓唬我的
How dangerous...
多危险
This is the last of the megadeath weapons.
这是最后的百万级伤亡武器
A huge bomb, nine megatons.
一颗巨型炸弹 九百万吨级
It has more explosive power than all the missiles fired from one of our nuclear-armed submarines today.
比现今核潜艇上的导弹 爆炸力更强
And could be detonated by a variety of ways:
可以通过多种方式引爆:
A spark, a lightning storm
火花 闪电风暴
or even a hit could set it off.
甚至是敲一下
But we have dismantled others like this...
但我们已经拆了其他...
Who were you talking to out there?
你在和谁说话
Ran into an old friend.
碰见了一个老朋友
Told you I'd come.
说了我会来的
Oh! Who is this?
谁啊这是
I'll tell you what I think, I'm gonna take you down to tracy and she'll give you a good haircut.
我带你去特蕾西那儿 给你理个好发型
Sounds like a good idea to me.
听起来对我不错
I say you just shave the whole thing.
我说 你不如全剃了
Make you look like a real man.
像个真正的男人
Smells good, ma.
闻起来不错 妈
You make enough for everybody? Between you and your brother,
够大家的份吗 - 俩兄弟吗
I never know who's gonna be here
我又不知谁会来
so I always try.
所以我尽量
Oh, and you can take some to your friends, too.
你也可以带些给你朋友
I'm sure they could use a good meal every once and a while.
我保证 他们偶尔也可以吃顿好的
Not trying to feed the whole neighborhood.
别试图养活整个街区
What's cooking, betty?
什么菜 贝蒂
Yummy. Come on, man.
美味 来吧 伙计
You know, it's strange,
这很奇怪
I never heard anyone knock.
我从来没听到有人敲门
Very funny, mr. D.
很好笑 D先生
You boys cut it out.
你俩闭嘴
Help yourself, john.
你自便 约翰
Thank you, betty.
谢谢 贝蒂
Hey, pass the eggs, man.
喂 把鸡蛋递给我 伙计
I ain't here to serve you.
我不是来服侍你的
Get up and get them yourself.
你自己拿
You looking for this?
找这个吗
What the hell, mom?
妈 搞什么那
The name of your band is
你的乐队叫
"white slave traders"?
"白人奴隶贩子"
We're all slaves to authority, ma.
我们都是当局的奴隶 妈
Get your ass over here and help me real quick.
死过来帮我 快点
Don't tell me what to do, I'm an anarchist!
别指手画脚 我是无政府主义者
Kiss my ass.
吻我的屁股
I would, but I don't want my lips to stink.
我会的 但我不想嘴唇发臭
Shit!
妈的
Why do we do this shit, man?
我们干嘛要这么做 伙计
'Cause it's fun!
因为有趣
This is work, not fun.
这是工作 不是乐趣
It's both.
都有
Plus, we're making a mark on this town.
而且 我们在替镇子做记号
This town don't give a shit.
这个镇子在乎吗
Shit, I know, but...
妈的 我知道 但是
That"amarillionare" gave us some extra cash.
那个"阿马里洛百万富翁" 多给我们钱了
Got to love that kooky bastard.
得爱上那个古怪蛋
Yep, he's always been good to us.
是的 他一直对我们很好
Yeah, I could definitely use the cash.
是的 现金用处很大
No, but for real, though,
说真的
what about you?
你怎么样
Man, I just want to start booking bigger bands, you know?
伙计 我只想开始更大的乐队
I feel like the scene's really picking up. - It's all possible, man,
局势在好转 - 一切皆有可能 伙计
you just got to get the bands to make the stop.
你尽管找乐队来制造这些停止牌
You just let me worry about that, all right?
让我来操心 好吗
Hey, you mind locking up?
介意锁门吗
Yeah, man, where you going?
伙计 你要去哪
I just got some shit to take care of, no big deal. Need a lift?
有点事要处 小问题 - 需要搭车吗
No, no, I'm good, I'll meet up with y'all later.
不用 我一会儿再和你们见
All right, man.
好的 伙计
Hey, I got a surprise for y'all tonight, too.
我有个惊喜给你们 今晚
I think I might know what it is.
我大约知道
Think it's ready?
好了吗
I think it's close.
差不多了
Whoo-hoo! What the fuck
搞什么
is up with your hair? Got ourselves a pretty one, boys.
你的头发怎么了 给自己理个好发型 孩子
What are you, an el chupacabra-looking motherfucker? What's up, dawg?
你是井中吸血怪吗 怎么了 伙计
What's up, baby? The fuck you say? Huh?
怎么了 宝贝 你TM说什么
Pretty-haired little pussy.
漂亮头发的娘炮
Oh, look at this little shit. Whoo-hoo!
看这小屁眼
I fucked a girl in jeans like that.
我插过一个穿这种牛仔裤的妞
Shit head!
屎头
Let's go! Let's go, ricky!
我们走 里奇
Fuck you!
操你妈
Damn!
妈的
Watch the jacket.
小心夹克
My bad, my bad.
我的错
You okay? Yeah.
你没事吧 没事
Chill out, it's all good.
冷静点 一切都好
Don't just sit there, get up and get the lady another beer.
别傻坐着 起来给这位女士再来一罐啤酒
What's this all about?
这是怎么了
This whole town is built to support the only nuclear weapons manufacturing facility in the nation.
这座城镇 是为全国唯一核武器生产设施而建的
Put it together, if you were going to attack america,
这么说吧 如果你要攻击美国
wouldn't you try to take out their most vulnerable weapons first?
不应先端掉他们最脆弱的武器吗
We got plutonium war heads under our feet as we speak.
我们说话当口 脚下正有钚弹头
This place is just a big target, ticking.
这地方是个大靶子 滴答
Ticking away.
滴答
Bomb fucking city.
炸弹之城
Thanks.
谢谢
Dude, of course.
伙计 不客气
Can you promise me something?
你能答应我一件事吗
I don't like promises.
我不喜欢承诺
Whatever,
没关系
just hear me out.
听我说完
Sure, go ahead.
当然 说吧
You may think this sounds cheesy or whatever...
你可能觉得俗气
Just...
只是
Please...
拜托
I...
我
I don't want you to leave here...
我不想你离开这里...
Without being armed somehow.
而不带武器
We need equalizers.
我们需要制衡
And not just you, I mean, all of us.
不只是你 我是说 我们所有人
So, what, like king and his police baton?
像国王和他的警棍吗
I think I can handle myself.
我想我能应付
I know.
我知道
But...
但
I don't know, like, dumb shit like this,
我不知道 像这样的蠢事
it happens all the time.
一直在发生
I'll just get, like, a rocket launcher or drive a tank,
我就带着火箭发射器 或者开坦克
then no one will mess with me then.
那就没人会惹我了
You know what I mean.
你知道我的意思
How about a bazooka, then?
那火箭筒呢
Shut up.
闭嘴
Grab this shit. Shit.
来一杯
Don't take it yet.
先别喝
Where'd you get this shit?
你从哪弄来的
I always have a secret stash.
我总是藏着秘密
Why you been holding out?
你为什么要藏
Because we hang around a bunch of fucking scavengers,
因为周围有一群清道夫
that's why. Let's shoot this shit, come on.
那就是为什么 - 我们喝吧 快
Son of a bitch!
爽
This is from my fucking stash.
这是我的藏物
You're the fucking scavenger. Boys, boys, boys!
你是TMD清道夫 孩子们
Yes it is. I present to you the beginning...
是的 我向你们展示...
Of brian's bitching brew.
布莱恩的私酿
This shit looks off.
这玩意看起来不咋样
Trust me, I know what I'm doing.
相信我 我知道我在做什么
All right, y'all.
好了 诸位
To the beginning!
敬开始
Knew that shit didn't look right.
就知道狗屎不对劲
It's potent, though.
太猛了
That's like over 14%.
超过14%
This shit is worse than I thought.
这玩意比我想的还糟
But... it'll do the fucking trick.
但...会获得成功的
14%,
14%
that's what I'm talking about
这就是我所说的
did I hit you?
你被我灌醉了吗
Oh, shit, we're out.
见鬼 光了
Move!
让开
What the fuck, bro?
什么鬼 兄弟
Victor, are you okay?
维克多 你没事吧
Hell yeah!
没事
Out with the old and in with the new!
旧的不去新的不来
Get this motherfucker a beer right here. Yeah!
给这混蛋再来瓶啤酒
Fire in the hole, bitches.
小心手雷 婊子们
You better run, motherfuckers!
最好快跑 混蛋
Oh, shit.
该死
I got you, bitch!
我抓住你了 婊子
Dude, this party's dead, man.
伙计 派对废了
You trying to get out of here?
想离开这里吗
Dude, don't overdo it, man, I only got a couple cans.
老弟 别太过火了 - 伙计 我只有几罐
Every time I go and get more,
每次我多买时
they give me a hard-ass fucking time.
他们就给我脸色
What kind of country has a law against how much fucking paint you can buy?
什么样的国家 有法律限购油漆的
Man, they got laws for everything.
伙计 他们有法律 规定一切
For the land of the free,
为了自由之地
you got to follow a lot of fucking rules.
你得遵守很多该死的规矩
Hey, yo, dude, dude, headlights, headlights, chill.
伙计 大灯 冷静
Fuck it!
他妈的
Shit! Fuck! Cops, cops!
妈的 警察
Come on!
快
Just got to outrun your ass.
赶快跑
Holy shit!
我靠
I think we did it, bro!
我们跑了 兄弟
Hey, where did you guys go?
你们去哪了
Dude, is the front door locked?
伙计 前门锁上了吗
The fucking cops are after us, man. Fuck!
该死的警察在追我们 伙计
I don't know, I'll check. What the fuck, y'all?
我不知道 我去检查一下 - 你们怎么了
What about cops? Get the fuck off him, bro.
警察呢 别管他 兄弟
Did they see you come here?
他们看到你来这里了吗
I don't know, man, they were right the fuck on top of us.
我不知道 伙计 他们就跟着我们
Fuck! Then why did you come here?
那你为什么来这里
Chill!
镇定
Will one of you shut the fuck up?
你们谁能闭嘴
Damn.
妈的
Fuck. They're right the fuck outside.
他妈的 他们就在外面
This is the apd, we know you're in there!
阿马里洛警察 我们知道你在里面
If you do not let us in, we will have to force entry!
不让我们进去 我们就强行进入了
I repeat, we will force entry! They're the fuck outside.
重复 我们会强行进入 - 他们在外面
You're fucking stupid! Why would you bring cops here?
你真他妈笨 为什么要引警察来
Wait, wait, wait, please shut up!
等等 请闭嘴
Damn it! What the fuck, bro?
该死 他妈的 兄弟
Get her the fuck off me, man.
让她滚开 伙计
Get her the fuck off me! Chill, chill, chill!
让她滚开 冷静
Stop! Unit base,
都停下
we have the perpetrators at 313 west 8th street.
基地 我们在西第八街313号有作案者
Request additional back-up,
请求增援
also request permission to force entry, over.
也请求允许强行进入 完毕
Stop.
停止
It's already too late. Late for what?
太晚了 - 什么太晚
Hey, hey, hey. Holy shit, dawg.
天啊 伙计
Hey, we were just tagging, bro.
我们只是喷漆而已 兄弟
Yeah, yeah, sure. Caught red-handed!
是的 当场被抓
Fuck you! Fuck you! Caught red-handed! Caught red-handed!
操你妈 抓现行了
Shut the fuck up, king. Chill, chill out.
闭嘴 国王 冷静点
John, shut the fuck up, dawg.
约翰 闭嘴 伙计
There's like seven cops out there.
外面有七个警察
Yo, I don't give a fuck!
我才不在乎呢
Hey, listen up.
听着
Shit.
妈的
You open this door,
开门
nobody goes to jail.
就没人进监狱
If you don't open this door, everybody's going to fucking jail!
如果不开门 每个人都要坐牢
You understand me? Shh. Shh. Shh.
你听懂了吗 嘘嘘
There's no point in cleaning up! Hey!
现在清理已经没意义了
We just need to act like no one's here.
我们得表现出没人来过
We wait 'em out, we wait 'em out. Yeah, dawg. Hey...
等他们出去 伙计
They need a fucking warrant to come in here anyways.
他们需要搜查令 才能进来
Y'all know that.
你们都知道
Check this out.
看这个
Chill the fuck out, all right?
冷静点好吗
You are such a fucking idiot, dude.
你真是个白痴 伙计
Shut the fuck up, bro!
闭嘴 兄弟
What, you gonna charge up on me, dawg?
怎么 你要怪我吗 老弟
This is gonna be fun.
有意思了
Just chill the fuck out... show us a fucking warrant.
冷静一下 请出示搜查令
Show us a fucking warrant!
请出示搜查令
We're just here for two men!
我们来这里 就为两个人
Give them up and you can go on about your night.
交出他们 你们可以照旧
Some bullshit.
尽说废话
Cops are such assholes.
警察都是混蛋
Goddamn it!
该死的
Look, look, look, we'll just sit here,
听着 我们就坐在这里
we'll wait 'em out, we make 'em go through the process, all right?
等他们走人 让他们走个程序 好吗
It's like 4 a.M.,
差不多凌晨4点
it'll take 'em forever to get a warrant.
他们永远不会拿到搜查令的
Nobody opens that door.
没人开门
Cut the power.
切断电源
Grab thumper.
操家伙
Show these motherfuckers what's up.
给这些混蛋看看厉害
Fuck this, I'm throwing king's ass.
妈的 我要把国王的东西扔了
I'm not going to fucking jail! Get the fuck off me, man!
我才不要坐牢 -  放开我 伙计
Shut the fuck up, man. Get the fuck off of me!
闭嘴 伙计 给我滚开
Will you shut the fuck up, fool?
闭嘴 笨蛋
I think they're leaving, dawg.
我想他们要走了 伙计
Yeah, yeah.
真的
They're leaving, dawg hell yeah!
他们要走了 兄弟
I told you assholes.
我跟你说了的 混蛋
They always fucking leave, man.
他们总是离开 伙计
Fucking haters! Shut the fuck up, man.
该死的 - 闭嘴 伙计
Fucking haters! They wouldn't just leave.
该死的 - 他们不会就这么离开的
That's weird, man.
那很怪异 伙计
Oh, shit. Dude...
该死 伙计
Dude, I think they cut the power.
伙计 我想他们切断了电源
No shit, you fucking idiot.
妈的 你这个白痴
Mm. Shut the fuck up, bro.
闭嘴 兄弟
What's up with the power, dude?
电源怎么了 伙计
On the ground! Freeze!
趴在地上 不许动
Head down! Hands up in the air! Now!
低头 举起手来 现在
You, get down, now!
你趴下 现在
Stop moving! You hear me? Freeze!
别动 听到了吗 不许动
On the ground now! Don't move!
现在趴在地上 别动
Stop right there! Halt! Down on the ground!
站住 停止 趴下
Get down!
趴下
Get on the ground! Now!
趴到地上去 现在
Freeze! On the ground, now!
不许动 趴地上 现在
Stop! Freeze!
站住 不许动
Get the fuck off of me!
给我滚开
Bitch! Bitch!
混蛋
Fall on the ground!
趴在地上
Get on the ground now!
地上 快
Get the fuck off me, fucker!
滚开 混蛋
Stop! Stop resisting! I'm not!
停止 别反抗 - 我没有
Hands behind your back!
手放在后面
Fucking pig! Get the fuck off me!
该死的猪 给我滚开
Get the fuck off me!
给我滚开
Shut your mouth.
闭嘴
I'm not your fucking kid, bitch!
我不是你孩子 婊子
Fuck you, man.
去你的 伙计
Fuck you!
操你妈
This is every day for me, bitch!
我每天都被这样
Get the fuck off me! Calm down, huh?
给我滚开 冷静点
Get the fuck off me!
给我滚开
Yeah, not so big now,
现在不猛了吧
are you, punk?
是吗 朋克
Get the fuck up.
快他妈的起来
Get in the chair. Fuck you!
坐到椅子上 操你妈
Now! Fuck!
现在 操
Get 'em on the wall! Get 'em!
让他们靠墙
Hands behind your back! Come over here.
手放在后面 过来这边
Fuck you! Fuck! Now.
操你妈 现在
Fuck you, bitch!
去你的 婊子
Get your hands behind your back.
把手放在后面
Hands behind your back.
手放在后面
You're a bitch motherfucker, dawg.
你是个婊子 狗娘养的
You think they give out a fucking medal for...?
你以为他们拿勋章是为了...
Fuck you!
操你妈
Get the fuck off me! I didn't fucking do nothing, man.
给我滚开 我什么都没做
Take that fucking badge off and say that shit, motherfucker.
把那该死的徽章拿开 混蛋
What are you gonna do now, punk bitch?
你要干什么 臭婊子
Take that fucking badge off and say it!
把那该死的徽章拿开
I didn't do shit!
我没做过什么事
We didn't do anything, we have rights!
我们没有做任何事 我们有权利
You lost your rights when you didn't let us in.
你不让我们进去 你就失去了权利
We didn't fucking do anything!
我们什么都没做
We didn't do anything! Show me the fucking warrant!
我们什么都没做 给我看搜查令
Judging by the looks of this place,
从这个地方来看
I'm sure all of y'all are guilty of plenty.
我敢肯定你们所有人都犯了很多罪
Fuck you.
操你妈
Sit still, you little shit.
别动 小混蛋
Spread 'em, sweetheart.
远离他们 甜心
This is not a game.
这不是游戏
Get your fucking hands off me.
把你的手拿开
Leave her alone, you fuck! She's a fucking girl!
放开她 你混蛋 她是女人
I said shut the fuck up! Fuck you!
我说了闭嘴 操你妈
On your fucking knees!
跪下
Looks like y'all are a bunch of real winners here.
看来你们都是真正的赢家
Fuck you!
操你妈
We didn't fucking do anything!
我们什么都没做
Get that the fuck off her!
放了她
Fuck you, pig!
去你的 猪头
I'm sure your daddy's proud.
你爸会为你骄傲的
Get the fuck off of her!
放了她
We didn't do anything! Fuck you!
我们什么都没做 操你妈
Ow! Fuck you!
噢 操你妈
You need to learn to shut your fucking mouth.
你得学会闭嘴
Fuck you!
操你妈
You want to die tonight, motherfucker?
你今晚想死吗 混蛋
Get the fuck out.
滚出去
Give him help on the wall, give him help on the wall.
帮他一把 让他们靠墙
Fuck!
操
Hold it right there, hold it right there!
按住他
Calm the fuck down! What's up, dawg?
冷静点 怎么了 伙计
You have the right to remain silent.
你有权保持沉默
Thought you said we didn't have any fucking rights?
你不是说我们没权利吗
You got quite a fucking mouth on you, boy.
你嘴巴真能说 小子
Fuck you! Fuck me?
操你妈 - 操我?
Fuck you, motherfucker.
操你妈的
Ah, fuck! Come on.
啊 操
How's that feel, bitch?
感觉怎么样 婊子
Calm down! Stop resisting!
冷静 别反抗
Fuck! Fuck!
操
Hey! You got any drugs? Where the drugs at?
有毒品吗 毒品在哪里
The fuck you'd say, motherfucker?
你说什么 混蛋
I have in my hand multiple police reports filed over the last four years.
在过去的四年里 我手头上有多份警察报告
All of these reports took place at the same establishment you frequented.
所有这些报告 都发生在你经常光顾的机构
Underage drinking,
未成年饮酒
multiple accounts of excessive noise,
过度噪音
multiple arrests, including minors in possession of alcohol,
多次逮捕 包括持有酒精的未成年人
minors in consumption of alcohol,
未成年人饮用酒精
public intoxication, drug paraphernalia,
公众中毒 吸毒用具
resisting arrest,
抵抗逮捕
and assault of a police officer.
还有袭击警官
Do you wish to deny any of these truths, miss hendricks?
你想否认以上吗 亨德里克斯小姐
Or do you believe that ending up behind bars is all a matter of circumstance?
还是你认为 坐牢全都是环境造成的?
They're so fat!
他们真胖
Look at him!
看看他
Aw, I want them all!
我都想要
This guy.
这家伙
He's, like, passed out.
他好像晕过去了
Oh, no.
不
Oh, my god.
上帝
I want him.
我要他
I want all of them. Oh.
我要所有的
Hey, hey, buddy.
伙计
He's so little.
他太小了
Come here, bud.
过来 小兄弟
I know how you feel, little buddy.
我知道你的感受 小家伙
It's no fun being locked in a cage.
被关在笼子里 一定不好玩
Oh, sweetie.
亲爱的
Gonna be like simba.
就像辛巴一样
What about"pistol"?
叫"手枪"怎么样
What about"shotgun"?
那"猎枪" 呢
No, none of those.
不 这些都不行
He doesn't like 'em? Uh-uh.
他不喜欢么
What is this,"destroy everything"?
这是什么"摧毁一切"
Filth.
污秽
Are you kidding me? You...
开什么玩笑 你...
Blatz. Shit split.
布拉茨(啤酒名) 分裂
Double cd? Are you fucking kidding me?
双CD 你耍我吗
I'm sorry, I don't know any of those.
对不起 我不知道这些
Oh, my god, I feel like I failed you!
天哪 我觉得我辜负了你
It hurts me on the inside that you don't know what that is.
你不知道那是什么 我心里很难受
Like...
像
Hell no.
不
The only thing that you failed at is naming a puppy.
你唯一失败的事就是给小狗取名
All right.
好吧
You give it a go. Give me him.
你来吧 你取名
Hi, puppy.
嗨小狗狗
So who the fuck is filth anyway?
那污秽到底是谁
It's the greatest fucking band in the world.
这是世界上最伟大的乐队
Come here.
过来
Mm, I'm not afraid of you.
嗯 我不怕你
What about"guinness"?
"吉尼斯"如何
I kind of fucking love that.
我喜欢
Except I hate it 'cause you came up with it.
但我讨厌 因为是你想出来的
So... ah!
所以
All right, wait, but we could still
等等 但我们还是可以
name him after the best beer ever.
给他取名为有史以来最好的啤酒
What about"stout"?
那"粗壮" 呢
He kind of looks like a stout. Yeah.
他看起来很粗壮 是的
You like that, buddy?
你喜欢吗 伙计
You want to be named"stout"?
你想被命名为"粗壮"吗(Stout 司陶特啤酒)
A-ha-ha."Stout" it is.
那就叫"粗壮"吧
I like it. Perfect.
我喜欢 完美
Perfect. Stout. I love it.
完美 粗壮 我喜欢
Hey, what's this? Hey!
这是什么
Dude... it's nothing,
伙计 没什么
I just keep lyrics to songs in it and stuff and just things I like and random thoughts I have.
我保留的歌词 还有随性记录
So it's like a fucking diary.
像日记
It's not a fucking diary!
这不是日记
It's just fucking lyrics and...
只是歌词和
Random ideas and...
随性的想法和
Fucking give it back!
他妈的还给我
I'll give it back on one condition:
有条件的
You read me something written by you and not another band.
让我看你写的东西 而不是乐队的东西
It's either that or you never get it back.
否则不还给你
All right, all right, just give it here.
好了 给我
You have to promise.
你必须保证
You have to say it.
你得说出来
I thought you didn't like promises.
我以为你不喜欢承诺
So?
怎样
All right, I promise.
好吧 我保证
But, like...
但是
You got to realize that...
你要意识到
I hear this to really loud music,
我听到的是非常响亮的音乐
and like...
就像
You know what?
你知道吗
Here, let me see that.
让我看看
Just...
只是
In my head, it's mostly screaming.
在我的脑海里 大多是尖叫
All right, you ready?
你准备好了吗
Yeah, go ahead.
是的 来吧
"My entire life,
我的整个人生
people try to rattle my cage to force me to explode from the inside out.
人们试图让我的笼子嘎嘎作响 迫使我内心爆炸
Testing me.
测试我
Trying to find my breaking point.
试图找到我的突破点
My mother would say, 'son, step in from the cold, '
我母亲会说"儿子 从寒冷中走出来"
and my father just the same.
我父亲也一样
He'd say, 'don't ever lose
他会说"永远别失去
your self-control.'
你的自控"
but I opened the window.
但我打开了窗户
I let the cold air flow.
我让寒冷的空气流动
I lost my self-control."
我失去了自控
Cody cates lived an honest life.
科迪·凯茨过着诚实的生活
Went to church every sunday.
每星期日去教堂
Played football.
踢橄榄球
He also was involved in many other extra curricular activities:
他也参与了许多其他课外活动
National honors society,
国家荣誉协会
student council,
学生委员会
fellowship of christian athletes.
基督教运动员团体
His family
他的家人
have always been proactive in the community.
在社会上 一直积极主动
Is this what they deserve?
这是他们应得的吗
They didn't ask for any of this to happen.
他们没有任何要求
So is this what they really deserve?
这就是他们真正应得的吗
Like, what are your plans now that the cheer season's over?
你什么计划 现在欢呼季节结束了
Cheer season doesn't end with football.
欢呼季节 不会随着橄榄球而结束
There are other sports. Yeah.
还有其他的运动 是的
Yeah, I mean, like...
我是说 像...
I meant, like, are you bummed now that the...
我的意思是 就像 你现在很沮丧
The football season's over?
橄榄球赛季结束了
Honestly, it's kind of exhausting.
说实话 这有点累人
You know, all the pep rallies and stupid sign making and stuff.
所有的动员集会 和愚蠢的牌子
Hey, this party's getting a little out of control.
这个派对有点失控了
Do you guys think the cops will come?
警察会来吗
No, don't worry about it, I told you,
不用担心 我告诉过你
cops never come.
警察从来没来过
Yeah, I mean, cops?
我是说 警察么
Are you kidding me?
开什么玩笑
Yo, we run this town.
我们主宰镇子
Run this town,
主宰镇子
bitches! Ooh-hoo!
混蛋
Oh, shit, man!
妈的 伙计
How you doing? Good.
你好吗 - 很好
How you doing? Oh, shit! I almost forgot to show you all
你好吗 我差点忘了给你们看
my latest and greatest.
我最新的和最伟大的
If, um... you'd all please accompany me to my ride.
如果 你们陪我到车里走一趟的话
Okay.
好
Ricky.
里奇
Got to be more like him, you know?
更像他了
I... this
我...这个
this is the greatest invention
这是最伟大的发明
since goddamn... coke.
自从他妈的可乐
Vicks... come on.
维克斯 来吧
Step on up here. Are you shit-faced, man?
到上面去 - 你搞什么 伙计
I'm cates, baby. Come on! Cates.
我是凯茨 宝贝 - 来吧 凯茨
Fuck, I'm drunker than a skunk.
妈的 我比臭鼬还醉
Get up there, motherfucker. Come on.
快上去 混蛋 快
Come on, put your mouth up on that thing.
嘴巴对着那东西
No, man, what the hell is this thing,
不 伙计 这到底什么东西
you crazy-ass redneck? Quit...
你这疯狂乡巴佬 别...
Being such a goddamn puss.
真是娘炮
Just...
只是
Put your mouth on the fucking thing.
把嘴对准了
All right, I'm going.
好 我来了
Yeah?
是吗
You're ruining my goddamn presentation.
你在毁了我的展示
All right.
好了
Ooh, god!
上帝
Man, what the hell? Is that fucking whiskey?
伙计 什么东西 威士忌吗
Goddamn right it's whiskey!
就是威士忌
I mean, that is the best fucking shit in the goddamn world whiskey, okay?
世界上最好的威士忌 好吗
It's not cheap, it's fucking expensive stuff so be goddamn appreciative, okay?
它不便宜 昂贵到死 所以感激吧
Now, see, I rigged the windshield wiper to flow whiskey straight into your fucking mouth.
现在 我用雨刷把威士忌直射到你嘴里
And you're so unappreciative, you little cock sucker.
你真是太不懂感恩了 你这个小鸡笨蛋
Davis, get your ass on up here.
戴维斯 轮到你
No, no, bro, I'm good. No, yeah, come on.
不 兄弟 我不用 - 来吧
No, screw you, dawg.
不 去你的 伙计
No, your football career just ended.
不 你的橄榄球生涯刚刚结束
You're officially retired, all washed up.
你正式退休了 一清二白
Come on, man. Cates!
来吧 伙计 凯茨
Drop your cock, and put on your sock.
放胆过来
Enjoy the fucking whiskey, please?
喝威士忌好吗
Thank you.
谢谢
Hey, how's it feel?
感觉怎么样
Like shit. We're not alone.
像大便 有人来了
All right, y'all, time to break it up.
好了 你们散了
Come on.
快
Party's over.
派对结束了
Get home safe.
安全到家
Yo, ricky.
瑞奇
Yeah? Where y'all headed?
是的 你们要去哪
Yeah, buddy.
是的伙计
Thank you.
谢谢
Tell the kids I said hi.
告诉孩子们 我打招呼了
Much obliged, y'all.
非常感谢你们
Hey, cody, can we give lindsey a ride home?
科迪 我们能送琳赛回家吗
Uh, hell yeah we can.
可以
Thanks.
谢谢
All right.
好了
Let's get the fuck out of here.
离开这里
Thanks again, guys, I appreciate it.
再次感谢 伙计们 我很感激
All right, y'all be safe.
安全回家
Hurry the fuck up, ricky!
快 里奇
Oh, my god.
上帝
Oh, shit.
该死
Damn.
妈的
What the fuck, man?
他妈的怎么了
Oh, you fucking bitch!
你这个婊子
Ugh! You motherfucker!
呃 你这混蛋
Fuck you, pussy! Fuck!
去你的 小妞
Fucking bitch-ass fucker.
他妈的婊子混蛋
We were minding our own business.
我们在管自己的事
Okay?
好吗
It was an all-out ambush.
一场全力以赴的伏击
Welcome to the party, my man. How you fucking bitches doing?
欢迎参加派对 伙计 你们在干嘛
Yeah, we're getting fucked up.
是的 我们要完蛋了
Look at this dumb piece of shit.
看看这个蠢货
Which one of you motherfuckers broke my window?
你们哪个混蛋打碎了我的窗户
Excuse me, faggot?
对不起 基佬
I said,
我说过
which on of you motherfuckers
你们哪个混蛋
broke my fucking window?
打碎了我的窗户
Do you kiss your boyfriend with that fucking mouth?
你用嘴吻你男朋友吗
Get him! Get him!
抓住他 抓住他
Get that motherfucker!
搞死那个混蛋
Get him!
弄他
Get him! Get off me!
弄他 - 放开我
Settle down, settle down.
安定
Come on, motherfucker.
混蛋
Get up. Come on, boy.
起来 小子
Get off me, man.
放开我 伙计
Now listen,
听着
I'd admire your spirit,
我很佩服你的精神
I really do.
我真的佩服
But you done... fucked...
但你搞...
Up...
砸了
Real... fucking...
真的...搞
Hey. Hey, you...
你
Bitch!
混蛋
Sorry I dropped my fucking chain on your face.
抱歉链子掉在你脸上了
Get him!
弄他
Get the fuck off me, man!
给我滚开
Get up!
起来
I will not stop
我不会停止
till every last one of you motherfuckers is six feet the fuck under!
直到你们中的每一个混蛋都入土
Wrath is on, motherfuckers!
愤怒来了 混蛋
Y'all better pray!
你们最好祈祷
Fuck!
干
Listen to me,
听我说
I know he can't hear us.
他听不到我们的声音
Damn. What the fuck, y'all?
妈的 你他妈的怎么了
What the fuck?
搞什么
Isn't that one of yours?
那不是你的吗
Looks like it went way past words.
看来已经成为过去了
Fuck this, dude, we need to handle shit.
他妈的 伙计 我们得处理烂摊子了
Come on, dude.
来吧 伙计
Let me see stout. I don't want any glass to get in his paws.
让我看看粗壮 我不想玻璃扎进他的爪子
I'm gonna set up, like, a little...
我要弄小....
House for him. Aw.
房子给他
I'll make him a brewery.
让他成为酿酒厂(粗壮=stout=某啤酒品牌)
Stout's brewery.
粗壮的酿酒厂
Damn, this fucker's heavy.
该死 太重了
One, two, three.
一二三
There we go.
来了
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
给我
Okay.
好
Be careful. Okay.
小心 好
Hey, buddy.
小家伙
Here, let me get him some food.
我给他拿点吃的来
You okay?
你没事吧
You like your new house?
喜欢新房子吗
Hungry?
饿吗
You hungry, buddy?
你饿了吗 小家伙
This is fucking bullshit.
狗屁
Yo, help me patch this up real quick.
帮我快速修补一下
Might be some nails lying all around.
可能周围有钉子
You got it? Yeah, yeah, I got it.
没问题 搞定
Let me get the other side.
我去另一边
Hold it up.
拿稳了
I'm holding it, dawg. The fuck?
稳的很 老兄 搞毛呢
No, just leave it. It's good.
行了 很好
Yo, where's the car at?
哟 车在哪
Oh, what the fuck happened to your face, bro? Holy shit.
你的脸怎么了 兄弟 我靠
John...
约翰
King! King!
国王 国王
What the fuck, dude?
搞毛呢 伙计
Dude!
伙计
What the fuck happened, man?
他妈的怎么了
It's all right, dude.
没事的伙计
You can tell me.
你可以告诉我
I've had enough, man.
我受够了伙计
I'm tired.
我累了
I'm tired of...
我厌倦了
Sitting around and...
坐在那里
Letting them act like we don't have a place.
让他们以为 我们无处可去一样
So I went down there to show them that we aren't gonna sit around and take anymore of their shit.
所以我去那里 告诉他们 我们不会坐着忍受他们
Let's even the motherfucking odds.
我们得扳回一局
I got a bad fucking feeling about this, man.
我真有预感 伙计
Shut the fuck up.
他妈的闭嘴
Yo! Shit's gone on too far, man.
太远了 伙计
That's what I'm saying. You said so yourself,
这就是我要说的 你自己也这么说的
we have to make a fucking statement. Yeah, dawg.
我们得做个该死的声明 是的伙计
We can't just sit here and act like everything's gonna blow the fuck over.
我们不能就坐着 装作一切会自行消散
It ain't gonna stop either. Next time, it could be you,
不会停止的 下一次可能是你
me, your girl or any fucking one of us.
我 你的马子 或者我们任何人
I'm going with or without you.
我不管你去不去
He's right, man.
他是对的 伙计
Shit's gone on way too fucking long.
该死的 太久了
You don't fucking know, there could be, like, a shitload of them.
可能有很多人
Then we fucking equalize it!
那我们就干掉几个
Yeah, fucking equalizers. Y'all need to calm the fuck down.
对 干掉 你们得冷静
Fuck this.
去他妈的
Brian! What?
布莱恩 干嘛
Look at this fucking place!
看看这该死的地方
Look at king's fucking face!
看看国王的脸
Let's fucking do this, yo. Let's go. Crass, come on.
我们动手吧 走吧 克拉斯 走
Hey, wait! What?
等等 干嘛
I'm sorry.
对不起
We need to be in this together.
我们必须一起行动
All right? We'll be fine.
我们会没事的
Come on.
快
Let's roll!
行动
Come on, brian!
快点 布莱恩
Let's fucking do this!
他妈的行动
Let's go!
我们走
Come on, motherfuckers!
来吧 混蛋
Go, go, go, go!
快
I don't remember.
我不记得了
Events of that night are blank.
那天晚上的事情 一片空白
Are they blank 'cause you had a couple of drinks to ease your nerves?
空白 是因为你喝了几杯 缓解紧张情绪
I mean, they were everywhere.
我是说他们到处都是
They were...
他们
Had weapons, had all kinds of bats.
有武器 有各种棍棒
I mean, we weren't expecting that.
我是说我们没料到
We didn't come for that.
我们毫无准备
I feel like...
我觉得
It was all my fault.
都是我的错
Fuckers, come on!
混蛋 快点
You know, it's a fucking pain in the ass every two weeks to have to beat one of these fuckers down.
每两周就揍扁他们一个眼中钉
Right? Am I fucking right?
对吗 我对吗
The stuff I recall is pretty hard to forget.
我记得的东西 很难忘记
And at that point,
在那一刻
it had been a while since I had anything to drink.
我有一阵子没喝了
Bye! Bye.
拜 拜
It's good seeing you. Have a good one.
见到你们很高兴 晚安
Yo, let's get up there.
我们上去吧
Ricky keeps blowing me up.
里奇一直在气我
These fights never would materialize.
战斗永远不会实现
One side would show up and everyone would gather in the parking lot
一方出现 每个人都会聚集在停车场
like a big, fun social event.
就像盛大的社交活动
That's what I thought was going to happen.
我就是这么认为的
But no one was ready for this.
但这次不是这样
I wanted to say something, but it was too late.
我想说点什么 但为时已晚
I wish...
但愿
It was just too late.
只是太晚了
Fucker, come here!
混蛋 过来
Come here!
过来
Come here, you fuckers!
过来 你们这些混蛋
It's now or never, motherfuckers!
要就现在 否则永不 混蛋
We end this shit tonight.
我们今晚就结束这一切
Come here. Come here, motherfucker
过来 过来 混蛋
come on.
快
Yo, what the fuck is going on? Yeah, let's just get out of here.
你他妈的怎么了 我们走吧
Fuck! Davis, davis, can we please get out of here?
戴维斯 我们能离开这里吗
Yo, just shut the fuck up, all right?
闭嘴好吗
Let me think! No, fuck that, we need to do something.
让我想想 不 他妈的 我们需要做点什么
We're fucked up! Wait!
我们完蛋了 等等
I'm a ninja in my caddy.
我是卡迪拉克内的忍者
Wait, cody, stop this! Stop it, we need to get out of here!
等等 科迪 住手 我们得离开这里
Shut up, no. Please, can we just get out of here?
闭嘴 不 拜托 我们能离开这里吗
Oh, my god! Oh!
上帝
Oh, my gosh, what...
天哪 搞...
Fuck! What are you doing?
你在做什么
Stop it, man, let me out of this fucking car!
停车 伙计 让我离开这该死的车
Holy shit! All right!
我靠 好吧
No, we're fucking going.
不 我们要走了
Get the fuck out of the way.
让开啊
W-what are you doing?
你在做什么
Get me the fuck out of this car.
给我滚出这辆车
No!
不
W-what are you doing?
你在做什么
Cody, stop this! Stop it,
科迪 住手 停下
we need to get out of here! Stop!
我们得离开这里 停车
Oh, my god! No, no, no!
上帝 不 不 不
No, you motherfucker!
不 你这混蛋
Fuck! Yeah, I bet he liked that one.
我打赌他喜欢
All right, all right.
好了
It's gonna be all right.
一切都会好起来的
You're gonna be all right, bro, just stay...
你会没事的 兄弟 别动
Stay with me. Call an ambulance!
跟着我 叫救护车
Somebody call the fucking ambulance!
快叫救护车
Is he okay?
他还好吗
He's dead, he's fucking dead!
他死了 他妈的死了
Not like this.
不是这样
Brian, sit up, cops are coming, man.
布莱恩 坐起来 警察来了 伙计
Don't you fucking die.
你他妈的别死
Don't you fucking leave me, man!
别他妈的离开我 伙计
Not like this.
不是这样
No!
不
What did you do?
你做了什么
What did you just do? Oh, my god!
你刚才做了什么 上帝
Oh, my god!
上帝
Lord, help me.
主啊救我
Help me.
帮帮我
Oh, my god.
上帝
Oh, my god, what if he's dead?
天啊如果他死了呢
What if he's dead?
如果他死了呢
Michelle!
米歇尔
Why?
为什么
What if you killed him?
如果你杀了他怎么办
What are you gonna do?
你打算怎么做
No!
不
Just... fucking wait, don't look at him.
等一下 别看他
Don't fucking look at him.
别他妈的看着他
Y'all don't have to go down with me, okay?
你们不用跟我一起下去 好吗
I'll, uh...
我会...
I'll tell them that y'all weren't in the car.
我会告诉他们 你们没在车里
But we were in the car!
但我们在车里
Michelle, I don't think you understand
米歇尔 我想你不明白
how serious this is!
这有多严重
Fuck!
干
No...
不
Not me.
不是我
Oh, god, no, please.
天啊 不 求你了
Mom...
妈妈
Mom, you and dad need to come up here.
妈妈 你和爸爸要上来
Western plaza.
西部广场
It's brian, something happened.
布莱恩出事了
It's bad, ma.
很严重 妈妈
I don't know.
我不知道
Please, just...
拜托 只是
Just come.
就来吧
I remember...
我记得
It being so cold.
太冷了
Unusually cold.
异常寒冷
And there was glass and metal everywhere.
到处都是玻璃和金属
It was chaos.
一片狼藉
It... it was worse than any nightmare.
比任何噩梦都糟糕
Cody's thoughts that night lay in intimidation,
科迪想 那晚躺着被恐吓
in fear.
怀着恐惧
But not hatred.
但不是仇恨
Yeah, but what he did is still wrong.
但他所做的仍然是错误的
And you cannot defend what he did.
你不能为他的所作所为辩护
Can I have the keys, please?
能把钥匙给我吗
Chuck.
查克
What? What do you got?
你有什么发现
We believe that the evidence will convince you,
我们相信证据 会说服你的
beyond a reasonable doubt, that this was not an accident,
除了合理的怀疑 这不是意外
that this is was not justified, and...
这没道理
And that the defendant intentionally...
被告故意
And knowingly murdered brian deneke.
故意谋杀布莱恩·丹科
He had never attempted to apply his brakes
他根本就没打算踩刹车
or turn his steering wheel
或者转动方向盘
as his cadillac had approached brian.
当凯迪拉克接近布莱恩时
He had fled the scene of a crime
他逃离了犯罪现场
and he lied to the police.
他对警察撒谎了
When the medical examiner
当验尸官
had described brian's injuries,
描述了布莱恩的伤势
he concluded that brian had remained conscious as his body was dragged under the... underneath the wheels of that cadillac.
他的结论是 布莱恩一直清醒 因为他的身体拖出了车轮
The impact...
影响
Impact so severe,
影响如此严重
that his collarbone had been torn free from his shoulder.
锁骨被撕裂 扯离肩膀
Our young people... on both sides of the aisle in this community
本社区两边的年轻人
need to be told by the 12 of you that what you do carries with it consequence.
需要12人陪审团告知其后果
No matter who you are.
不管你是谁
No matter what you look like.
不管你长什么样
And no matter how you dress.
不管你穿得怎么样
I don't expect
我不指望
you to enjoy sending this young man to prison.
你们享受把这个年轻人送进监狱
I don't.
我没有
I expect you to do it with a tear in your eye and your heart in your throat.
我希望你们 能噙着眼泪 心跳到喉咙口
President john kennedy said,
肯尼迪总统说
"we do things,
我们做事
not because they are easy,
不是因为它们容易
but because they are hard."
而是因为它们很难
Today I ask you to do the hard thing.
今天我请诸位 做一件困难的事
I ask you to send a message to this community
我请你们 给这个社区一个信息
that all young people, all of them,
所有的年轻人 所有的他们
will suffer the consequences of their actions,
会遭受自己行动的后果
and that you are holding cody cates
你对于科迪·凯茨
unconditionally responsible for the death of brian deneke.
对布莱恩·丹科的死 负有无条件的责任
"Destroy everything."
"销毁一切"
Is this the message we want to send our children for generations to come?
我们想发送给后代们 如此信息吗
"Destroy... everything."
"摧毁一切"
Ladies and gentlemen, this is not a case about diversity or tolerance,
先生们女士们 本案并非寻求差异化或容忍
this is not about judging people for the way they dress.
不是为了评判人们的着装方式
This case is about a gang of young men who chose
本案是关于一群年轻男子 他们选择了
a lifestyle designed to intimidate those around them, to challenge authority
一种生活方式 来恐吓周围的人 挑战权威
and to provoke a reaction from society itself.
并激起社会本身的反应
When those punks brought bats and chains out there with them to western street that night,
那天晚上 那些小混混把棍棒和铁链 带到了西街
a conspiracy was put into play to kill and maim those high school students.
用来杀害和残害那些高中生
Cody had no time to think or ponder,
科迪没有时间思考
he had to take immediate action and he took it.
他不得不立即采取行动 并付诸实施
And if he had to live it all over...
如果他活着
He would do it again.
他会再做一次的
You see, what cody cates faced out there that night
诸位 科迪·凯茨 在那里面对的那一夜
was a bad combination:
是糟糕的组合:
A mean drunk with a weapon.
卑鄙的酒鬼带着武器
And somewhere,
在某个地方
in the infinite processes that shape a boy into a man...
在无限的过程中 塑造男孩变成了男人
Something happened to brian deneke.
布莱恩·丹科 出事了
The manner of his death was, unfortunately,
他的死亡 很不幸
the end result of a long list of poor choices over the last six years of his life.
在他生命最后六年里 一连串糟糕选择的最终结果
You could even argue that he was destined to die the way he did.
你甚至可以争辩说 他注定会那样死去
He was a violent individual.
他是个暴力的人
And it took violence on cody cates' part...
对科迪·凯茨付诸了暴力
To put an end to further violence and to save an innocent life.
为了结束未来的暴力 并拯救无辜的生命
Let this boy go home.
让这个男孩回家吧
Restore him to his family.
返回他的家庭
'Cause he did the right thing.
因为他做了正确的事
The one story that, uh...
一个故事
That really struck me
这真的打动了我
and got me thinking about this was, a few years ago,
让我想起了几年前
there was this teenage punk rocker kid who was run down by a white jock in dad's cadillac.
有个十几岁的朋克小子 被白人运动员 开着爸爸的卡迪拉克撞倒了
And, uh... this boy died because he looked different.
这个男孩死了 因为看上去面目全非
So this thing happens, this guy kills this kid,
这家伙杀了这个小子
and is clearly guilty,
显然是有罪的
you know, his guilt is admitted,
他被定罪了
and guess where this all-american athlete is,
猜测这个全美运动员
he's in college.
当时在上大学
You know, the jury felt the punk rocker deserved to die
陪审团觉得这个朋克 活该去死
because he looked the way he did.
似乎他就该这副样子
And not only was he killed, but then, in the trial,
他不仅被杀了 在审讯中
he was killed again because they...
他又被杀了 因为他们
You know, criticized his lifestyle
批评他的生活方式
because he didn't, you know, wear a tommy hilfiger shirt
因为他没有 穿汤米米希尔菲格牌的衬衫
and khaki pants, you know?
还有卡其裤
And then the killer was even applauded at graduation
凶手甚至在毕业典礼上鼓掌
because he was a football star.
因为他是个橄榄球明星
The american dream,
美国梦
strong, normal.
强壮 正常
He never a spent a day in prison.
他从来没有在监狱里呆过一天
So who do we blame?
那我们该怪谁呢
You know?
你知道的
Everybody wants to say, you know,
每个人都想说 你知道
"too much violence, too much violence today,"
"太多的暴力 太多的暴力今天"
you know?
你知道的
Did everyone forget about the civil war,
每个人都忘记了内战
or the bible, or shakespeare, you know?
或者圣经 或者莎士比亚
Violence isn't brand-new.
暴力不是全新的
That's why I asked the question, you know?
所以我才问这个问题
I put this up on my website.
我把这个放在我的网站上
I said,"is adult entertainment killing our children,
我说"是成人娱乐 杀死了我们的孩子
or is killing our children entertaining adults?"
还是杀害孩子娱乐了成人呢"
I think that's kind of the question
我认为这个问题
we got to ask ourselves today.
我们今天要问问自己
And, yes, ask yourself that every time you watch the hungry cameras at the crime scene,
是的 问你自己 每次你通过犯罪现场的饥渴摄像头
or at the funeral, or at the plane crash.
或者在葬礼上 或者在空难中
You know, I'm in a square right now. You're looking at me,
我现在就在框框内 你正在看着我
I'm looking at myself in a monitor, you know?
我在监视器里看着自己
We sit in front of the tv and we are the tv.
我们坐在电视机前 我们就是电视
We're a copy staring at a copy...
我们是一个副本 盯着一个副本
At a copy and a copy.
无穷的副本
Eventually it's a xerox that's so degenerated,
最终像施乐复印机般堕落
we don't know which came first.
我们不知道 谁是始作俑者
And that's where we are.
这就是我们的处境
And that's what I'd like to leave you with.
这就是 我想留给你的
Don't tell me what to do,
别对我指手画脚
I'm a fucking anarchist!
我是他妈的无政府主义者